The Dynasty Hotel
is mismanaged.
And because of that,
the management
is closing the hotel
at the end of the month.
- [EMPLOYEES MURMURING]
- [GASPS]
We will release your
separation pay immediately.
We hope 30 days is enough
to find a new job again.
Ma'am, that's not right!
What are you doing here?
You're already fired!
To get my last salary.
Well, you're fired again.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRENDA ON VIDEO]
(Speaking in Korean) You bitch!
- [HANNAH ON VIDEO] Ma'am...
- You bitch!
- No wonder...
- [EMPLOYEES MURMURING]
It's because of you again!
[MRS. SONG] We took care
of the hotel's legacy.
And yet, Dynasty's
reputation is wrecked
because of your cheap stunt!
But, ma'am,
it's not their fault.
[EMPLOYEES MURMURING]
They give their all...
everything to this hotel.
Because of her harassment...
abusing my kindness here,
you only have one week to pack,
- Oh no!
- or else...
I'll forcefully evict you all!
- Ma'am, please...
- [EMPLOYEES MURMURING]
Mrs. Song! Mrs. Song!
Ma'am!
Seriously, Hannah?
Stop it already!
Don't play hero!
You're just making
things worse!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mrs. Song! Mrs. Song!
No, ma'am, please!
- Manager.
- I need this job!
[EMPLOYEES MURMURING
IN THE DISTANCE]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
I've heard what happened.
I promise to talk to Mrs. Song
and make things right.
I want to talk to the chairman.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I want to talk to my father.
[MUSIC BECOMES DRAMATIC]